♪ ♪
♪ LYIN' ISN'T BETTER
THAN SILENCE ♪
♪ FLOATIN', BUT I FEEL
LIKE I'M DYIN' ♪
♪ STILL, NO MATTER WHERE I GO ♪
♪ AT THE END OF EVERY ROAD ♪
♪ YOU WERE GOOD TO ME ♪
♪ YOU WERE GOOD TO ME, YEAH ♪
♪ I KNOW IT'S EASIER TO RUN ♪
♪ AFTER EVERYTHING I'VE DONE ♪
♪ YOU WERE GOOD TO ME ♪
♪ ♪
♪ LEAVIN' ISN'T BETTER
THAN TRYIN' ♪
♪ GROWIN', BUT I'M JUST
GROWIN' TIRED ♪
♪ NOW I'M WORRIED FOR MY SOUL ♪
♪ AND I'M STILL SCARED
OF GROWIN' OLD ♪
♪ YOU WERE GOOD TO ME ♪
♪ YOU WERE GOOD TO ME, YEAH ♪
♪ AND I'M SO USED TO
LETTIN' GO ♪
♪ BUT I DON'T WANNA BE ALONE ♪
♪ YOU WERE GOOD TO ME ♪
♪ YOU WERE GOOD TO ME,
YEAH, OH ♪
♪ GOD ONLY KNOWS WHERE
OUR FEARS GO ♪
♪ HEARTS I'VE BROKE, NOW
MY TEARS FLOW ♪
♪ YOU'LL SEE THAT I'M SORRY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU WERE GOOD TO ME ♪
♪ YOU WERE GOOD TO ME ♪
♪ ♪
♪ AND NOW I'M CLOSIN'
EVERY DOOR ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I'M SICK OF
WANTIN' MORE ♪
♪ YOU WERE GOOD TO ME ♪
♪ YOU WERE GOOD TO ME, YEAH ♪
♪ SWEAR I'M DIFFERENT
THAN BEFORE ♪
♪ I WON'T HURT YOU ANYMORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU WERE GOOD TO ME ♪
♪ ♪